const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'How do I join the conference?',
        answer: `All interested participants can view the ICDM program, however only registered participants will have access to the video conferencing links for each session, therefore registration is required to join ICDM virtually and is currently open. `
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Cost of Registration',
        answer: `No,Registration will be paid for  all participants`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: ' missed online registration, what to do?',
        answer: `Send your interest on email `
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'How do I submit my Abstract?',
        answer: `end your Abstract as per the guidelines on email id`
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: ' When will we receive login instructions?',
        answer: `When a virtual attendee registration is complete (paid for) you will receive an email with access instructions. Please be sure to test your system before the start of the conference.        `
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: ' Can I submit more than one paper?',
        answer: `Yes, more than one research paper by the same participant is allowed. Although it should be noted that they will be charged separate entries at the conference and charged accordingly.`
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: ' Can I register if Iâ€™m not associated with an institution/agency?',
        answer: `Yes. ICDM encourages students, independent researchers, and freelancers to participate. Affiliation with any company, institution, or agency is not required.  `
    }, 
    {
        id: 8,
        question: ' Can more than one person present with me?',
        answer: `No, only a single presenter is allowed. However, we encourage other authors to be available to answer any questions.`
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: ' How do I get an invitation letter so that I can apply for a visa?        ',
        answer: `You will get one from the DTU administration once you successfully submit your paper.`
    }, {
        id: 10,
        question: ' What length should my abstract proposal be?',
        answer: `Please keep proposal abstracts for both sessions and papers to no more than 250 words.`
    },
];
export default questions;